TAN HENG WAI

Fullstack Web Developer

INFO

ADDRESS

No 743, Jalan BPJ 3/11, Bandar Puteri Jaya, 08000, Sungai Petani, Kedah

PHONE

+0164500596

EMAIL

mushroomweii@gmail.com

<u>LINK</u>

GITHUB

https://github.com/HunterWeii

LINKEDIN

linkedin.com/in/tan-heng-wai-969aa1bb

SKILLS

FRONTEND

Javascript / Typescript
React / React Native / Vue / Next
HTML5 & CSS3 / SASS

BACKEND

Node / Express / .NETCore C#

Microservices / REST / Mysql

Others

Git, Github, Jira, Scrum, Rust Blender

PROFILE

Spent 5 + years pursuing on web development industry. I have develop strong interest and passion on Frontend development especially on Javascript application. I always looking for a new ways to keep myself updated and grow as a T-Shaped developer.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Frontend Developer, Easywork Sdn Bhd

Penang

Jan 2021 - Nov 2021

Responsibility

- Maintain in house Chat application with nodejs and reactjs.
- Working and maintaining Easywork hub website.
- Setup theming file, write reusable UI component and work with UIUX designer for updating latest UI.
- Document UI component with Storybook.
- Volunteer on AdaKerja.my project to help people find job during covid period.

Senior Fullstack Web Developer, Thunder Print Sdn Bhd

Sungai Petani, Kedah

Jan 2020 - Jan 2021

Responsibility

- Mentor and provide support for junior developer
- Research on various frontend technology such as PWA, Webpack, SEO practice
- Follow up latest trend and best practice

Global Printing E-commerce Project

- Setup website from scratch with nextjs and react
- Build reusable react component
- Document components with storybooks
- Involve in UIUX design process to provide feedback for UI design and workflow
- Collaborate with backend programmer to workout the data model and API design
- Integrate API with frontend application

EDUCATION

Computer Science University Tunku Abdul Rahman

May 2010 - Dec 2014

CGPA: 2.7

Information Technology Tunku Abdul Rahman College

May 2007 - May 2009

CGPA: 2.7

Fullstack Web Developer, Thunder Print Sdn Bhd

Sungai Petani, Kedah

Jul 2017 - Jan 2020

Web Printing Editor

- Build a fullstack printing web application for customer to design their artwork.
- Solve complex frontend component architecture problem and state management problem.
- Design backend REST API to communicate with frontend app.
- Build application to convert printing data into printing ready PDF file using Node JS.

Printing E-commerce Store

- Support and maintain existing e-commerce website.
- Implement optimization technique for browser, web and performance.
- Collaborate with UIUX designer to revamp website UI.

Mobile Application

- Refactor native mobile app into hybrid app using React Native
- Build microservices API for mobile and web useage

Internship For Javascript Developer, Piktochart

Penang

May 2017 - Jun 2017

Motivation

- Learn how to code Javascript in larger web application.
- Good opportunity to learn from proffesional.

IT Engineer, Perusahaan Sindi Sdn Bhd

Sungai Petani, Kedah

April 2015 - April 2017

Responsibility

- Build and maintain web portal for internal user.
- Build static swimming website for company
- Provide IT support

Internship for Web Developer, Resonet

Penang

Oct 2014 - Dec 2014